He is pissed right now.
Yeah, he is.
Keep your head on a swivel.
Oh, yeah.
We're leaving,
bro. We're leaving
-Uh-huh.
-Chill pill.
They kill more people
than lions out here.
Every step forward's
a step closer.
You know, we made the
decision to move on to hopefully
greener pastures, because
if we post up camp here,
he will come out at
night, and that will be
the end of our challenge.
That won't just be the
end of our challenge.
That might be the
end of our lives.
But, you know, moving sucks.
Ah!
-Jesus.
-Careful here.
We have been walking for
miles and hours in the sun.
We're exhausted.
We're all dehydrated.
But we can't stop.
We're getting
close, guys. I feel it.
Does it look like it's
opening up up here?
-I see rocks.
-Oh, yeah.
I see some sky up ahead.
I'm seeing a waterhole.
-There's a freaking boat.
-What?
Who knows what
the... That's just weird.
And there's something standing.
This is a big old cage.
What is this thing used for?
This is wild.
Problem is, we don't have a
choice to go anywhere else.
This is the top of the
map, and that's scary.
I'm wondering whether
that cage is worth
keeping something in
or keeping something out.
What the heck went on here?
Three weeks into
the 35 day challenge...
It is scorching out right now.
...a stifling heat wave
swept across the land...
Maybe we should stop
and just take a big drink.
...forcing the survivalists
to rethink their strategies.
We have to leave
here eventually.
Let's leave here when
we're in the strongest
-position possible.
-All part of the way out.
Escape this wasteland.
Waz and Teal headed
north on a multi day trek...
Look at this. Fresh water.
What's up? Good to see you.
...only to encounter Joe...
-Where are your people?
-I am my people.
...alone in his barren
camp for the last 17 days,
where they help
secure the area's
last remaining protein.
Whoo!
-There we go.
-Oh, man! Cheers!
First meal caught
and shared together.
Six terrapin out of
Joe's pool of water
is pretty enormous for him.
But this whole
area is just trashed.
We've made the
decision we have to leave.
We would love to
have you come with us.
-We gotta go.
-I don't know about go yet.
Ooh, I like that washer.
I'm out here at the
ruins, as Joe calls it.
It's like a hunting
lodge that they have
pretty much pillaged.
But looking around
here, I can see why people
are not here anymore...
there's nothing here.
This whole desolation is just
so engulfing, and
even Joe's place,
maybe even more so.
We have a long way to go
to escape this, and I think
perhaps it's getting
worse before it gets better.
-See that tree over there?
-Yeah.
I can hear some buzzing
around it, but I wanna check out
if there's some honey
in there that we can get.
That would be awesome.
I think any survivor gets
excited when they think
of the idea of honey.
And if we have meat,
meat dipped in honey,
that's calories and pure joy.
Joe, have you made your mind up
-whether you come with us or not?
-Man, I'm still
tossing it around.
This is the hardest place
to ever have to survive.
So, if they wanna get
out of here, I understand.
But they haven't spent the
time that I have to study it,
to understand it, but
they don't I don't know
the amount of time
and energy and effort
that I've put into this.
There's still a
chance, and I just need
to take that chance.
And you can see...
just there, there's
some drippage coming
-out of the tree.
-Yeah.
There's a chance, just
like right inside that trunk,
-we've got some honey.
-There's a huge chance.
-Yeah.
-I mean, you can see it
oozing out, so
I think this, uh...
-I think it's worth it.
-It's totally worth it.
-Ready?
-Ready.
'Cause there's no
food around here,
our jerky supplies are
definitely diminishing.
I think we can just maybe
get a little bit of honey today
and maybe just move on.
If there's no animals here,
there's nothing here for us,
we're gonna go
where the animals are.
Looks like it's
coming from here.
I can't... let me just...
I'm not even 100%
sure that it's not tree sap.
There's no sweetness to it.
I think this mission is
gonna be unsuccessful, Joe.
Yeah, once I realized it's not
honey, I'm down off that table
pretty quick and ready to go.
But also, in the back
of my mind, I knew
that that juice is not
worth the squeeze.
Just have a look myself.
I'm not willing to give up.
I don't think it's sap.
I think it's whatever
nest that was, you know?
Could've been termites,
could've been ants.
Peeling this back a little bit.
You can see there's just
like tons and tons of it.
I really, really want this.
Oh, this juicy goodness.
Joe's in a different
place for me.
I don't know whether a little
worm's crawled in his ear
and started burrowing into
his brain, or what's going on,
but he's had to scavenge
every single calorie out here,
and it hasn't been a lot.
-Oh.
-You good, buddy?
I don't need your
passing out up there.
I'm not falling
down from up here.
I just... just need a minute.
All right, welcome back, brain.
One of the benefits of
having done so many
of the challenges is you
can see different angles.
I think he can only see the
one angle, one perspective.
He gets a goal in his mind,
and he's stubborn enough
that he wants to achieve it,
but, if he's not getting
enough calories in,
and he takes one wrong
step, falls over, hurts himself,
that could take him out.
I think that might be it, buddy.
I don't think there's any...
it don't look like
there's any left.
Yeah, let's take it
back, make a cup of tea,
-see if we can all share that.
-All right.
Uh.
All right.
I got this cup
full of dirty sap.
Just try and get as much
of the dirt out of it as I can,
get it down to its
sappy goodness.
We got something,
I don't know yet,
but might have some sugar in
it, might have some calories in it.
Can you make a tea?
Mix it with some pine
leaves or something?
Yeah, and that'll be...
be something today.
That's just weird, man.
But, as far as nighttime
shelter, that's prime time.
I don't wanna stay in that cage.
You know, that was a rough hike.
I'm fatigued and maybe
even a little dehydrated.
None of this makes sense.
-No.
-Like, I can't... I can't put a backstory
to this situation.
All we know is that there
is an abandoned boat
in the middle of a water
hole next to a big cage.
Was this greener
pastures? Jesus Christ.
Once home to a large
wild game reserve,
this area is scattered
with abandoned
hunting outposts and equipment.
Cages like this were used
to protect game animals
from predators
before they could be
introduced into the wild.
Do I feel, you know,
kind of weird sleeping
in a freaking
cage? A little bit.
But do I also wanna
get eaten by a lion?
Not really.
I'm perfectly fine with
sleeping right here.
All right, man. Whatever,
whatever you want.
Well, I'm sleeping
in the cage with a fire.
I'm just thinking of safety, so.
It's a boma that's already made.
Ah!
We just did this... insane hike.
And, if we have to spend the
next two hours hacking down
-acacia thorns...
-Yeah.
-...it would kill us.
-Yeah, it would.
It would kill us. We
would be left unsafe.
Yeah.
My first thought was, "No
way in hell, I'm sleeping
in that cage out here."
But now I see the light in
this dark situation, I'm in,
'cause I don't think I have
the energy at this point
to actually build a boma.
What do you guys think?
-Yeah.
-I'm kind of digging it now.
-We're cool.
-That takes care of tonight.
-Yeah.
We got our sleeping stuff.
We can make a fire in there.
We'll get some firewood.
We'll shut the door.
We're good to go.
I might try to get
some food tonight, too.
-OK.
-Yeah.
What are you thinking? Fishing?
-Put some lines out?
-Yeah, just find some bait
and get some lines in the
water and see what happens.
Yeah, that's important.
You got a good-sized
beetle in there.
I can see him
moving right there.
This thing's worthless.
After weeks of fishing
frustration... Screw that.
...due to a
territorial crocodile...
It's absolutely
beaten the out of us.
Wes and Steve's
dam project finally led
to a much needed win.
Oh, oh! Yes!
What do you got?
-You are kidding me?
-Yes!
After all this time,
man, you did it.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm gonna leave these
lines out as passive lines.
Maybe something will come along.
Yeah, we haven't
put some effort in.
You all right, buddy?
I see his head right now.
We are still battling the croc,
and it's a risk every time
we go down to the water
because he knows where
we fish and he could be
lurking anywhere.
And so we're really battling
hard to make sure that we're
being as safe as possible
while still able to procure wins.
Let's hog the inside
of the lake, real quick.
Take one more just
little glance, see if there's
anything possible,
moving or to eat.
Oh man, oh man.
Good gosh!
We're just not
seeing anything, man,
except for two crocs now.
We finally get a fish,
and now we have
multiple crocs in our pond.
It just makes me hesitant
to get back in the water.
I don't need to come up
missing a leg or something.
I'm not sure what
we're gonna do here.
So the main thing to get done
is to make sure that we have
a fire and that
we can boil water.
The clock's ticking, and
the sun's going down.
There we go.
-Here's a nice burner.
-Nice.
A load of termites on it, too.
Sweet.
Look at that.
What have you found, Frank?
-It's a fish carcass.
-Catfish?
-Yeah.
-Awesome.
-Bait?
-Yeah.
I can get the rest
of the firewood
if you wanna get
that bait in the water.
-Yeah.
-We'll divide and conquer here.
It has been a really
hard and long day.
We've had a big hike. We
expended a lot of energy.
So getting food on the
table at this point in time is
incredibly important.
-Hurry up and wait.
All right.
Have you started
wrapping your mind around
if you do come with us,
what you're going to bring?
I'm making a
mental inventory Yep.
About what that would look like.
You know, it, uh...
you know, it's just something
I got to work out still.
A lot of... a lot
of things, right?
If I stay, there
will be trouble.
You know, the
goal will be double.
There's goals, but there's no
resources to achieve the goals.
And you can always
bring your goals with you.
-They don't weigh anything.
-They don't.
Regret is the weight
I don't wanna carry.
Fair enough.
Joe, you're boiling over.
Bubbling over.
Trying to strain this
juice through a cloth here.
Sorry.
Blew it.
Blew it. Sorry.
It is what it is, as long as
you didn't burn yourself.
If I had a guess, we
lost maybe 20 calories.
As I'm watching Joe, I start
to realize if Joe doesn't decide
to come with us tomorrow,
that's only gonna end one way.
He won't be able to make it out.
He won't have the energy.
He'll probably keel over,
and no one will be here
to save him.
But if he chooses to
stay, he chooses to stay.
He's a grown man. He
gets to make his own calls.
Does anyone wanna
scorpion hunt with me?
No.
Tomorrow, we're
gonna hit the roads.
We don't have any energy
to waste, so we need
to conserve, hydrate, and rest.
Whoa! You all right?
Hey, did you pass out? Medic!
Come on!
Medic!
All right, so does anyone
wanna scorpion hunt with me?
No.
I'll go scorpion hunt with you.
OK.
Whoa, you all right?
Hey, did you pass out?
-Medic!
-Hello.
-Come on!
-Hey, what?
No, no, no, dude,
you passed out.
-OK, hold on.
-No, I'm fine.
-No, you didn't. Medic!
-what?
Dude, you passed out
and you mashed your face.
Oh, no, it's
fine. It's just dirt.
But I don't think I hit my head.
I think I just hit
my little eyebrow.
-You did hit your head.
-I just hit my eyebrow.
That's part of your head.
OK. All right. All right.
-OK.
-Just stay sitting down -for a little bit. -Sit.
-Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
-Sit.
I'm fine.
Stand up too quick,
man. That's what happens.
Yeah, yeah.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
-No, no, no, no, no.
-I'm just helping.
No.
Da, da, da, da.
Ah.
When I passed out,
it hit me like that.
I got up, I took a few
steps, I leaned over,
and that's the next thing
I remember was Teal
calling for the medic.
How you doing, buddy?
-How you feeling?
-So, I feel fine.
We've just been called
out to assess Joe,
who's experienced
a syncope episode,
which is an episode of fainting.
Just gonna check
your blood pressure.
Not seeing any spots
or any blood vision?
No spots, no blurry vision.
I can see these scratches
on my arm, very superficial.
Not any blood Got
a little bump here
-on the eyebrow.
-All right.
Maybe some
abrasions, I don't know.
Mnh-mnh.
We suspect that he's
going through a bout
of heat exhaustion.
He needs to stay hydrated
as much as possible
-and keep out of the sun.
-Alrighty.
But we will be monitoring
him very closely
for signs of concussion.
But he is vitally
stable and good to stay
in the challenge.
-We have drinking water available?
-Right there.
OK, have a sip and
stay in the shade.
OK, thank you.
-For me?
-Water.
-Tea.
-Thank you.
Thanks for caring
about me, Teal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna pick three pieces,
and each will have their choice.
Joe, eat some jerky.
So hopefully that helps your
brain and body.
Joe has recovered a
good bit from that fall,
but he's been at such a
calorie deficit for so long,
that it's getting a bit scary.
That came out of nowhere.
It really did. I
did not see stars.
I did not need to breathe.
It was like lightning.
You know, if that happens
while you guys are away,
then I'm screwed.
So, you know, it's a big
reminder of what survival is
and sometimes it means
relying on other people,
you know, especially when
getting this close to the end
and we got nothing
but fumes in the tank
-and we got each other at least.
-Yeah.
I think I wanna leave
this place behind me.
Are you ready to go?
-I am ready to go.
-Mm.
There is not a damn thing
left here for me to find,
discover, uncover, or
thrive or survive off of.
It is just a wasteland,
and it is time
-to leave it behind.
-Yeah, Joe's coming.
-Yeah.
-Whoo!
Yeah, this place wants
to just eat you alive, man.
It just wants to open up
and swallow you up whole.
So if we stay together
as a group, push on
and see what adventures await.
All right, pack your things.
A bit of a roller coaster of
emotions, but we've achieved
what we want to achieve in
talking Joe to come with us,
and now it's time to leave.
We're gonna make sure
he's got enough fluid in him,
need a couple extra
bits of jerky, just so we're
physically ready for
what's gonna be probably
a pretty tough journey.
I gotta say, Teal, it
was really nice to see
-your face when I woke up.
-Shut up.
I'm serious.
You know, buddy, as
much as I love our shelter,
I think we're gonna
have to move on.
Yeah.
We're just not catching enough
to survive.
Yeah.
So we're in agreement
on that, right?
100%?
It's time to leave Cell Block B.
Try to rest up,
try to hydrate up,
try to get one more good win.
-Yeah.
-And then we just set out.
Yeah.
All right, I'm
solid on that plan.
Yeah, I'm down with that.
I'm very down with that.
With multiple crocs in
our pond, we just have
to keep our nose
to the grindstone.
And so Stee and I
set to making a couple
of deadfall traps.
We're gonna really
concentrate on eating
everything we possibly can.
And we're gonna see if
we can catch some critters.
All right, I'm gonna
search for a good rock.
The classic figure
four deadfall trap
combines a bait stick with
two other notched sticks
in the shape of a four,
and held in place by the
weight of a large stone.
When an animal
goes for the bait,
it triggers the trap,
releasing the stone
that pins the animal.
Yes, it'd be real
easy to be stable.
When you're this deep
into a challenge, every meal,
every win, is
extremely important.
All right, Stee.
There we go, buddy.
Thanks.
This is where I saw
a bunch of squirrels.
So I'm gonna choose
this little area right here
and put my trap.
We wanna go through
this challenge with energy
and the only way we're
gonna be able to do that
is if we somehow score
some dribs and drabs of food.
We're just gonna have to
see. We're just gonna keep
hitting it, keep
hitting it every day
until something breaks.
I've got some reconstituted
rib meat from the nyala.
It's really on a hair trigger.
And the squirrels
I saw in this area,
if they decide they
want some nyala meat,
they're gonna get a
good thump on the head.
What a day. What a day.
Hell of a day.
It's pretty close to
the end of the day,
and there's no telling
what can come up tonight.
We didn't have time to
cut any acacia thorns.
Something could totally
grab us through these bars.
If anything does come,
I'm hoping it's just a hippo
or an elephant and even then,
something that big can
probably move this thing.
Boom.
So tonight is gonna
be an adventure.
-Be careful, hey?
-Yeah.
Oh my God, you got it!
-Yeah!
-He got it!
It's a big one!
-Oh my God!
-Hell yeah, Frank!
Frank!
Holy!
Hell yeah, buddy.
Look at that.
I stoned him right
through the freaking spine.
-That's a decent catfish, too.
-That's amazing.
All right, so we
gotta gut this quick.
-Yeah, we do.
-This is dangerous.
-Yeah.
Yoohoo!
Steven, how stoked are you?
I'm super stoked, look
at Frank's win, man!
I know.
Brand new location, first day.
Frank comes in like
freaking Robin Hood
and just stones a
catfish. I am just so
absolutely very proud of him.
-This is all meat.
-All meat.
Meat, skin.
Oh, my God.
That is delicious.
Now, the thing is, this
smell is gonna bring
-animals towards us.
-Yeah.
Night 22, and we are settled in.
The three of us
are lockstep now,
and we'll be ready
to go in the morning.
This challenge for me has been
nothing but struggle and
the endurance of hardship.
But with these two awesome
people who came in, like,
it made...
made a change in how
I'm seeing our ability to...
to make it through this
apocalyptic hellscape.
And there could be just a
better space down the road, so...
This was the inciting
incident I needed just to see
a different perspective on
what life can be out here.
-Hyenas?
-hyenas.
That behind me,
those are hyenas.
We can't see them.
It's pitch black.
We are literally
the zoo attraction
in the bush right now.
Usually, the animals
are in the cages.
We are actually in
a cage.
And we are
surrounded by the most
fearsome predators in Africa.
Crazy.
-Do you have the map?
-Yes, ma'am.
Moving day.
You got to get moving here
pretty quick before the sun
burns through these clouds
and it gets even harder
to do this.
I feel stronger than ever
with these two by my side.
So let's pack up,
hit the road, and, uh,
find our next destination,
something new.
All right, so we're here.
Obviously, this is our end goal,
but, um, we wanna
break it up a little bit.
I think the smartest
option is we just go
to the closest water source,
and then we can just keep going,
or we can just
stay there the night
to see what resources
are available.
Still 11 miles from their
targeted destination,
the new team of three will veer
northwest in hopes of finding
a suitable waterhole to stay
the night before continuing on.
Their path will be marked
by dense, thorny brush
and rocky terrain, home to
packs of aggressive hyenas
and the venomous puff adder,
whose expert camouflage results
in more fatalities than any
other snake species in Africa.
I think we should be
able to get this done,
hopefully before the sun
breaks through, but maybe not.
All right, so quick as
we can. Backpacks on.
Get our backpacks
and get out of here.
Now we start to head
out into the unknown.
We don't know what
we're walking into.
We have to rely
on all our best skills.
As a group, we're gonna test
what we are as survivalists.
Not only do we have to
worry about all the predators
through the areas
that we have to trek,
but we also have to worry
about a dude with a wheelchair.
-Wheelderbeast packed up.
-Real question.
-Do you need that wheelchair?
-Yep, for sure.
You guys don't
trust that it rolls?
I want to bring the wheelchair
so I can carry my water,
my bow, my arrows,
my cutting tools,
and the fish basket.
I may have to
ditch all this stuff,
depending on the terrain
and where we're going.
So it's a gamble, but I
know it'll be useful in the end.
I think Joe is determined
to make his wheelchair
make it through the journey.
It's not my favorite
survival item.
I think wheelchairs don't
really belong in the bushveld,
especially since they
could make our hike
slower and longer.
All right, guys, let's do this.
Let's roll.
I like what you did there.
Well, it certainly
was the shelter in hell.
That does look so apocalyptic.
Priority number one
right now is to get
our sleeping situation
as safe as possible.
We do live in a cage,
but it is not secure.
Um, I mean, the holes are
big enough for a lion to grab us,
for a hyena to grab us.
So I need to do a
boundary of Acacia thorns
around the perimeter.
That's gonna keep us safe.
There we go.
I could definitely use
some more acacias.
I'm not thrilled about
sleeping in a cage, but, uh...
it is a dark, scary
place out here.
And last night, we heard hyenas.
So we have no choice
but to make it work.
Yeah, buddy, that's a big boy!
At the same time, I'm
also gonna work on,
um, some shading for the
roof. I'm gonna be cutting down
a lot of green foliage.
A lot of surface area up there.
Stacking that up on top.
Do you want any
in particular first?
If you want, you can
just throw them over here,
-and I can grab 'em.
-Oh, OK, cool.
There you go. Boom.
Perfect.
At the Thunder Bome, we
learned a valuable lesson
by not having protection
from the elements.
Oh, this is wet.
The roof would be
nice right about now.
I don't know whether
I'd call it survival
or just suffering.
But, look, it's a mistake
we won't be making
again in the future.
-All right, last one.
-Last one.
-OK, I got it.
-Got it?
Yep.
Phew.
How's it looking there?
Look pretty shady?
-Really good shady?
-Yeah.
Good.
How's the acacia look
from the inside? Good?
This side looks awesome.
This side still needs some work.
Yeah, we're gonna
fill that up a little bit.
-But that looks awesome.
-This is good... this is safe.
This is actually
comfortable in here.
You did good. We did good.
Good. Phew!
Oh, my gosh.
The sun is something
else right now.
Yeah, no kidding.
So this cloud cover did
not last as long as I hoped.
We're not making
an amazing time,
but we're kicking along
as well as possible.
These hikes, we're pushing
into an unknown space
and there's still
predators around.
The heat's coming down.
We've also got a lot
less energy in our bodies.
We've got less
water in our bodies.
Every single small
mistake can be magnified
-into a big mistake.
-Waz, where you go?
You go that way?
-Yeah, it was this way.
-OK, sorry.
That just looks
really clean to me.
It does.
We're trying to pick the
smoothest path possible.
Ooh, good one.
Ish!
Ouch.
Wanna try and just
move with the sense
of purpose here?
OK.
I am struggling to get
this wheelchair through,
but every push that goes
and every good wheel rotation,
I'm grateful for the
amount of material that I get
to push forward.
-The water.
-Go forward.
You missed the wheels.
You kinda go backwards over it.
-Like a normal one?
-Should have.
You want help?
No, I'm good.
We are out here to survive,
and the clock matters.
So trying to find our footing
and clearing the
path so that Joe
can move his wheelchair down it,
this is a pretty
enormous challenge.
All right, I gotta do a reset.
Basket fell off.
How the did that happen?
Oh, the rope broke, that's why.
That's gonna fall apart, too.
Let's switch it
out there. All right.
It's so hot here,
and I'm exhausted.
Like, I'm not having fun.
Because, truth be told,
two people and a wheelchair
don't go very fast.
Looks like the
bushes are thinning
out up here a little bit.
Ah.
-What happened?
We lost the wheel. Ugh!
Looks like the bushes
are thinning out up here
a little bit.
Ah.
-What happened?
-We lost the wheel.
We've been going slow
since he has a wheelchair,
so incredibly frustrating.
This slipped out.
The whole thing
slipped out, so...
I got some washers in my
bag. You think they'd help?
I don't have a bigger one,
but I have one that'll bridge
the gap between those two.
All right.
But we have to figure
out a quick solution,
'cause now we're running
behind, and we need to get going.
-Does it rotate?
-It will.
Teal came through
with the perfect washer
that she just had.
She'd been collecting
washers this whole time.
It's that kind of thing
you only get with a group
of survivalists and people
that have an engineering mind.
OK, good, we're back
in biz. Thank you, Teal.
-Yep, you're welcome.
-Who would have known?
I tend to do that.
Just keep walking.
Yeah, it is hot again.
It's kind of like
your standard day
-in South Africa, right?
-Yeah.
That's my trap, you see it
right there in front of you?
Nothing on either one?
No.
Nothing.
Sure.
Imma eat some mopani
leaves, real quick.
Yeah, roger that, mate.
My deadfall was
empty this morning.
You know, that's how it goes.
But right now, I'm trying
to add anything to my diet
that I can.
You know you're down to
survival when you're eating
mopani leaves, 'cause
there's no joy in it.
I know mopani leaves put
some kind of calories in you,
but damn, they're disgusting.
If it wasn't for being in an
absolute survival situation,
I wouldn't even come near 'em.
I think we're about out of food.
To get out of here,
we're gonna have to hike,
and it's a long way.
And so we know, not getting food
is not helping our cause. Yeah.
Resources are drying up quick.
It's hot now. Hot like wasabi.
-I'm getting thirsty, man.
-Yeah, me too.
All right, we'll find
some shade up here.
We'll stop and have a
break. I wanna check the map.
Ooh.
Yeah, so that big tree
right there, the one...
the furthest one we can
see, I think it's gonna be
right around there somewhere.
There's a lot of big
green trees there.
-That's a good sign.
-Yeah.
You guys good to
make this one last push?
-Now?
-Yep.
Oh.
Five more minutes
and we're sitting down.
-I don't believe you.
-That's all right.
Have I steered you wrong before?
We've been hiking
for forever, it feels like.
I'm about as exhausted as I get.
Waz is a legend, and
his decision making
is sound, but it feels a
lot like we are wandering
aimlessly at this point in time.
What is this?
Guys, look at this,
look at this, look at this.
-Wow. -Someone has been using this.
-...No kidding.
It's a shelter.
-Hello?
Hey, look at that.
That is a water
hole, and it's big.
What more can you ask for?
-I wonder where this person is.
-Let me see the fire.
It's been doused with water.
It says the Thunder Bome.
Oh, the Thunder
Bome, that's pretty cool.
That is way cool.
It's a big cool old car.
Can you imagine moving all this?
Think they got
a little lucky here.
Very nice.
A little bee smoker.
Maybe they found bees?
I like that we
have the protection
from the predators
already built in.
Yeah.
-But if it rains...
-Yeah.
It's not nice.
All right.
Well... keep going, or
we can just stay the night.
I don't know.
It's one night.
Yeah, well, I mean,
we'll make it work.
It's just one night,
Whoever was here
was quite comfortable.
So it doesn't make
sense they left.
Other than, you know,
the elements just got them.
Or maybe, I suppose,
the predators?
They either tapped out or were
pushed out by something here.
It's kind of eerie.
This is a nice, secure boma.
So what's pushed them out?
Why have they left so early?
Have they been pushed
out by elephants, lions?
What's going on? Are
we at risk, you know?
If they've left because
they feel like they're at risk,
are we at risk?
What pushed them away?
Well, most of the
push-away stuff
comes in the night,
so we'll find out.
All right, so it's the night,
and we are currently staying
in someone else's boma.
This is gonna be a really
good boma to protect us
from any animals on the outside,
but there is zero
protection from any rain
that might happen,
any wind that happens.
We can put up with this,
'cause it's just one night,
but we're just gonna
pack up and keep moving,
because that's what our plan is,
not staying here anymore.
Try to get the wheel going.
Naked in a cage. It's sick.
Dude, I have no fear.
Holy.
Look at that, out there.
Holy crap.
These gaps right here
are definitely big enough
for us to be grabbed
and pulled through.
They won't pull
us totally through,
but they will rip off our limbs.
How you doing,
Joe? Almost there?
I am almost there, yeah.
Let me wire in my
water, throw in my quiver.
Oh, we need to look at the map.
Yeah, I got the map here.
We're obviously
right this one here.
-Yep.
-And with this weather,
we can travel fast and we
can travel long distances,
so I'm thinking
straight shot north.
You know, it's just gonna
follow this ridge line here.
It's gonna bring
us in on this water.
With favorable cloud
cover, the team plans
a straight line path to the
northernmost waterholes,
just over seven miles away,
leaving them eight miles
from the edge of the wasteland.
This boma was fun for a night,
but a night's enough for me.
We're gonna head on the road.
Teal, you all packed up, yeah?
Yeah, I'm good to go.
I gotta grab a couple
more things inside there.
I'll be honest, I'm exhausted.
The journey yesterday was
excruciating, and now we are
covering more land
than we've ever covered.
It promises to be a long trek.
I'm ready to go, I
just gotta throw in
some things on the top.
I mean...
-Maybe I'll take a car and put the wheelchair in the trunk.
-There we go.
Yeah, I think
that's a good idea.
Yeah, I gotta grab
one more thing.
Joe looks like he's
got some extra stuff.
I don't know how that's gonna
work over some rough terrain,
but we're just gonna
have to play it by ear.
Some of the unique
stuff that I found
in the Thunder Bome...
there was a grease
gun, a lot of wrenches.
My mind's been trying to figure
out what I could do with that.
But we're getting
to the end here,
and the cart's already
full, so, it's time to move on.
I'll always remember it
being, kind of, probably
the most unique boma.
Three out of five stars
would change a lot of things.
Let's get a move on.
Tomorrow's a big move,
and now we're just
counting down the hours.
Like, we can't wait
to get outta here.
Where we're at,
there are no resources.
They are dried up, done,
washed up, finished.
And we can't stay here.
We'll starve to death.
So tomorrow morning,
we're moving on.
I can see our deadfall
traps from here.
They're both up.
Check the lines.
Yeah.
You got any final
words for the croc?
Yeah.
Hmm.
I was just caught on the bottom.
I'm gonna go turn over a
log and see if turning more...
Big frogs. Yeah.
Yeah.
And we wait.
Come here, dude... come here.
Yeah.
-Yes.
-Alrighty.
Alrighty. We eat
for another day.
That's a win,
baby. That's a win.
Yes.
All right, we got
some work processing,
so we'll check in later.
Thank God for this
cloud cover, man.
Just keep pushing, guys.
Can't be much further.
All right.
We're on the last
little leg of this journey.
Uh, we've been blessed
by the clouds overhead.
But the terrain's got tough.
It's hard for me
to walk through.
There's thorns everywhere.
I can only imagine
how hard it is for Joe.
Ooh, I'm gonna have to
help you down here, Joe.
Oh, craps.
-Can you lift that?
-It's still attached.
I'm gonna help you.
I'm gonna lift it over.
-Yep.
-Not gonna lie.
-Not moving very fast.
-Down.
All right, go ahead and go.
Go, go, go, go.
One last push,
guys. One last push.
-You seeing anything yet?
-Nothing yet.
We've been hiking
for forever, it feels like.
I'm just putting my feet in
each footstep that Waz takes
and hoping that one more
step will get me closer.
Oof.
Looks a little clearer
up ahead, Joe.
I'm excited to see what
we've got here, but...
I have a feeling there's
a lot of work to be done,
and I'm afraid I'm gonna
get there exhausted.
What is this over here, people?
-Oh, is that water?
-What is this over here?
This is something
man made down here.
-Come on... go, go, go.
-Oh, my gosh.
What is this? Another
half built shelter.
Wonder if anybody's here.
Hello? Hello?
-Oh, my God!
-What's up, buddy?
-Is that naked people?
-Whoo!
Whoo!
-Hey!
-Yeah!
What's up? What's going on?
Hello?
-Oh, my God!
-What's up, buddy?
Is that naked people?
-Whoo!
-Hey!
Yeah.
Shoot, we were wondering
if we were the last ones left.
That's 'cause you
didn't know I was here.
Seeing Waz, he's...
one of my best friends.
We spent 60 days in
the Amazon together,
over 40 days in Africa together.
We've wrestled anacondas.
We've swam with piranhas.
We've faced down
hyenas and lions.
-What's up, buddy?
Brother! Hell yeah!
Obviously, I've spent
a lot of time out here
on these challenges with Steven.
And to know that he is
still here in this hellscape,
I'm not really surprised.
We got here two days ago, man.
We moved, like, maybe
seven miles away.
Where did you come from?
We come from Thunder Bome.
-Did you see it?
-I stayed there last night.
Did you? Awesome!
What can we help you carry?
Give us something to carry.
That's all right, you
wanna take the water
-and the walking stick?
-100%.
I was wondering if there
was another female left.
Oh, me too.
I know that I could have
gone the rest of this challenge
with just Joe and Waz,
but, at this point in time
in the challenge,
having a female around
just kind of feels comfortable.
I finally feel like the
adventure begins now.
Yeah.
I love the fact that another
female has walked into camp.
And she's obviously a badass.
And to see another
woman out here surviving,
I know what it's been
like for me out here,
to see somebody
else... that's epic.
That's a... look at you go.
Yeah, well, Joe,
he kind of stumbled
out of the brush
looking like a hobo
kicking down the street
somewhere with a shopping
cart full of goodies.
Has it been a ride?
-17 days solo.
-Yeah? 17 solo.
Yeah.
So, saw some impala
hooves in the food truck.
Yeah.
-Yeah, I killed an impala.
-That's great.
Been shooting catfish
out of this water.
Yeah.
But I see more bows,
more arrows, and I see
a fish trap and a mosquito
net and, you know, all this stuff
could be useful. You're
almost there, buddy.
Is this anybody's
reserved parking spot?
-Anywhere you want.
-All right, cool.
Boop boop!
Well, welcome to the rage cage.
So you got here a
couple of days ago?
-We got here day before yesterday.
-Mm.
I don't even know what to think.
I'm seeing something
that I've never seen before.
I'm not prepared for
it. There is a cage.
So we got all this up, most
of this stuff up yesterday.
Like people in a cage
in an environment
as dangerous as Africa...
It... we... what are
we walking into?
Let's get this organized.
Pick a side or a corner,
wherever you guys
wanna sleep.
A moment after realizing
that we have a cage out here,
I immediately clock
in on the water,
which means
constant animal activity.
A group of six humans could
be very tempting for anybody
in the area that
hasn't eaten in a while.
I honestly am firing off
back and forth in my mind
on how we're gonna make
that a safe and protected shelter.
It's gonna get cozy in here.
As long as
everything's organized.
Yeah, we can move that later.
So let's just get the
fire sorted and then
-shift everything around it.
-There it is.
What are you guys thinking?
Fire in the middle, everybody
around the perimeter,
or leave the fire where it
is, and we can just boom,
boom, boom, boom, boom.
Just leave the fire where it is.
Yeah, then we can all face it.
Perfect... and whatever
doesn't need to be in here
can be out there.
When groups come
together in these extended
day challenges, you
got more hands on deck,
you got more people that
can take on responsibilities.
But I've never met Joe before.
I've never met Teal before.
I don't know
their personalities.
I don't know their work ethic.
And without us all
working together,
till we escape this Africa,
we are still surviving,
we are still in danger 24/7.
Where's everyone going?
So we've just been hanging
out down the back end.
So do you wanna
take the middle spots?
Can I get top bunk or what?
You can have top bunk.
From being out
here all by myself
to having Waz and Teal come in,
to now we have more
people that can share
and work out hunt strategies.
And so it's a total
game changer mentally
that I'm still kind of
wrapping my head around.
The next question is, "What
is this cage doing here?"
What are we protecting
ourselves from
that we need this for?
Yeah, well, we heard
lions, we heard hyenas.
It'll protect us from
everything, you know,
except like a big,
pissed off bull elephant.
-I guess we'll find out.
-Yeah.
This cage is my worst nightmare.
I can't believe it.
Look at all that food
we're gonna have.
Yeah. How you feeling, Wes?
Oh, like a million
dollars, man. This is great.
Look at all that meat.
All that meat.
Me and Wes...
There's not like a
ton of meat on that.
But, damn it's delicious.
I mean, it tastes like
somebody put spices on it.
It's unbelievable.
Every bit of it.
Nothing goes to waste.
Yeah, it was.
Yep, really good win.
We are sleeping in our cage.
I don't know how big
it is. It's not big enough
for six people, but
there's six of us in here.
It's pitch black.
I can't see what's
happening around us,
but it's just gonna be
one of those nights.
We can hear some
incredibly angry elephants
...the one thing
that could us up
is an angry bull elephant, so...
Oh, my gosh.
We are here in the
new Rage Cage Boma.
This morning, we woke up
and already were thinking
shelter adjustments.
It is a tight little
cage in there,
and I'll be honest,
it was a long night,
and I didn't get a lot of sleep.
How'd everyone do last night?
Like, I know we're pretty
packed in here, but...
it was bad... horrible.
We were like sardines.
And then, on top of
that, we heard last night
lots of elephants,
angry elephants.
So this little waterway
here that we're on
is a super active little spot,
and there's a lot
bigger threats here
than previous camps.
I've seen what elephants can
do to trees, and in my opinion,
if they can do that to trees,
then they could probably
stomp our little cage.
So, I think we need to
make some changes.
We gotta figure out something.
Yeah, it's time to
bug outta this place.
Yeah.
You know, the only
thing I'm gonna miss
about this area really,
when we move, is our shelter.
Stee and I put blood,
sweat, and tears into making it
as good as it is.
And I know that we're
not gonna have that
when we show up
at our new location.
From their current camp,
Wes and Stee will head
northwest toward a
collection of water holes,
five and a half miles away,
pushing through exposed
stretches of burned out bushveld
before heading
into low hill country,
where black mambas
slink through the thick grass,
and steep, rocky outcroppings
provide the perfect ambush
conditions for leopards,
who can cover over
20 feet in one jump
and take down prey
three times their size.
If they make it, they
will remain eight miles
from the edge of the wasteland,
which must be crossed on day 35
in order to escape
and reach the nearest
outpost of civilization.
Yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
When we start talking
about migrations,
then you gotta start thinking
about what you take with you,
what you leave behind, what
you can carry legitimately.
The wire, I would
really like to keep.
I'd like to make a harness.
For the walk outta that.
Thanks to eating the
terrapin, it gives you a nice
little boost, but we're
getting ready to move miles.
And as hard as this
survival challenge has been,
I'm really going
to be struggling.
I'm happy with what
we're taking, mate.
Yeah, I think it's a
good selection of stuff.
It's not too much.
Me and Wes have
been so proud and happy
how bomb proof our shelter is.
We might not find
these resources
to build a roof again.
We gotta start from scratch,
that's gonna burn
a lot of calories.
All right, boy, what you say?
Let's do it.
All right.
Cell Block B.
Out.
If I'm going too fast,
Wes, gust let me know,
'cause I'll just
go off in the zone.
All right.
I'll tell you if I'm
lagging behind.
You hope you're going to a
spot that has more resources,
but really, you might end
up in a spot that's worse
than where you came from.
And unfortunately, you
don't know the answer
until you get to
your new location.
So, I'm thinking last night,
since we were like sardines,
how can we kind of modify
this without man made objects,
kind of extend our
real estate a little bit?
You know, getting a key
amount of sleep out here
is incredibly important
when it comes to escaping,
-you know, this hell on earth.
-Is that wide enough?
Yeah, I think that's good.
But it's hard to cram
six people in a tiny cage.
Uh, you know, things I
thought I'd never say in my life,
but, um, it's the truth.
So we need to
extend the rage cage.
I figured we'd wrap a boma
around it like a horseshoe
with about four foot
high, three foot wide
of acacia thorn.
I figured we could start
a fire outside the cage,
which is gonna keep
us safe from pretty much
every wild animal.
And being outside of the cage,
um, you know...
definitely risky.
But, in this situation, this
is really the only option.
And if a big wild animal comes,
we can literally jungle-Jim it
up the top of the cage.
-We have to beef it up.
-Yep.
Lock off this entire area
here to make a fortified wall.
-Little fortress.
-Yep.
We know this is
a lot of hard work.
Expending calories.
At the same point in
time, this will just give us
a little bit more
room and availability
for extra fires, and everyone
can be nice and close
to a heating source.
Nice.
Well, we're gonna go hunt,
gonna find a water source,
hopefully with some tracks.
Yesterday, we made
it to our new area,
but because of
so many predators,
there's no way any
animals are coming down
to the water source
that we're camping at,
so I'm gonna head up
what looks like a dry creek,
see if there's
another water source
that's gonna draw
some animals in.
Oh, boy.
Look at what we have here.
Oh.
That's a hippo.
That's the most
dangerous killer out here.
Holy moly.
Oh, there's three?
Oh, man, it looks
like there's a big male.
This is his territory.
He's gonna be very
territorial about it.
I bet, since it's so big, I can
find a spot with some tracks.
I just have to be
very, very careful.
OK, seeing some action.
Got some scat,
some antelope dung.
I think they're
drinking from here.
And that's really promising.
Well, I think up here
on the top of the berm,
this would be the
place to set up.
I can watch the hippos,
and then have a nice shot
of the whole shorelines.
All right, my hippo buddies,
we're gonna be
hanging out a little bit.
There's a big risk here,
having such a large,
uh, aggressive predator.
But, uh, this is gonna be the
last big push before escape,
so we need to get big wins.
Yeah, nothing left to do
now but just sit the blind
and, uh, keep hoping
for the best out here.
Blazing hot, dude.
Blazing hot.
So really, I'm trying to
just keep a nice, slow pace
so we don't break out in a
sweat, lose any more water
than we need to.
Heat's here today,
that's for sure,
and not much cloud coverage.
Maybe one wispy cloud
every now and then.
Other than that, it's
direct sun beaming down
on us, and we've got no
choice but to push forward.
And you know I
don't like the sun?
Oh, I know you don't.
Water...
It's getting a lot harder
to walk in this area now.
Lot of high grasses.
This is definitely
snake territory.
I'm just being real careful
where I step, buddy.
I totally get it, mate.
Terrain so far, is,
uh, it is ever changing.
Big mountain, a rocky crop.
Yeah, that's a big one.
You can tell we're getting
into some more hilly land,
and we're going into
uncharted territory now.
So we wanna
stay to the left of it?
Yeah, I think we
keep walking up.
-Yeah.
-That is leopard central.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, jeez.
Yeah, and you can't see 'em.
They can jump out at ya.
Hey, there's a death
scene right to your left too.
-See that skull?
-Yeah.
Jeez.
Look at all these
bones everywhere.
Yeah, there's plenty here.
Everything's dead.
I think we gotta
be really observant.
Yeah, we'll just keep
our eyes on swivel.
Let's be real quiet,
a little stealthy.
I got a bad feeling.
Hey.
I see something straight ahead.
Look at that!
Whoa.
2 Hey.
I see something straight ahead.
Look at that.
Whoa.
There's some
rubble and a building.
It looks like a pretty big one.
You wanna go check
it out? We'll see.
I mean, what in the world?
Those are massive.
-Dude, this is an old processing station.
-Yeah.
Like a butcher shop, basically.
Once part of a large
hunting reserve,
this compound was
used as a supply outpost
and processing station
for large game animals.
Yeah, I'm up for that.
This place is creepy as hell.
Just 'cause you know that
death was everywhere in there.
Sheesh.
Maybe it is...
lack of water, same
reason they leave everything
behind over here.
-Lions and used to be malaria.
-Yeah.
What the is that?
Oh!
Like that.
Hey, the sun is hot.
Steve and I have
walked all morning.
We haven't found water yet,
so even though we're
exhausted already,
we've got to keep pushing on.
Wherever we set
up our next shelter
has got to be based on location,
and that location
is... water source.
All you can do is keep going.
I'm afraid we still
got a ways to go.
I'm feeling good
today. It's coming today.
I don't know.
There's something 'bout the air.
It just feels right.
Dammit!
Goddammit.
Just seeing an animal
come to the water, and then,
you know, I didn't
get him, and he ran off.
All right, so I'm gonna
get out of here before...
I gotta walk in the
dead of the heat.
It's good to try a new
water hole, but, um,
you know, I'm trying to
hunt so that we can have
a bunch of food, 'cause that
would help everybody out,
but I'm walking
out empty handed.
-Ready?
-Yep.
-Where do you want it?
-Let's see that back end.
Yep... yeah, we'll get
one more over there.
Gotcha.
-There we go.
-Yeah, that's perfect.
Boom. Nice.
That should be good enough.
Definitely adds
to the rage cage.
We got a good start.
We can improve on it.
But I'm very glad
that we expanded.
Probably two or
three of us outside.
I know me and Waz
are gonna be out there.
And that should be more than
enough room for everybody.
All right, take a little break,
chill out for a bit, hydrate,
little bit of shade,
because it is
scorching out right now.
Ever since arriving
here at the Rage Cage,
I've been wondering
about this old boat.
It doesn't look like
it's a running boat,
but I feel like underneath
it might be serving
as a nesting spot for catfish.
So, I'm gonna go check it out.
Catfish build nests in
shady underwater hollows,
such as rotted logs or
even discarded debris,
lining the hollow with
mud and vegetation.
After the female lays her eggs,
the male remains to fiercely
protect the eggs
until they hatch.
This is crazy.
It's a little nice
one over here.
Yeah, yeah, right there.
There's, like, a
little hole there,
that they like to lay in.
Might find a nest under there.
Yeah.
But, uh, it is right in
the heat of the sun.
There's only one spot on
the back right of the boat
where there is some
sort of a catfish nest.
And it gave me the
idea of standing above it
and seeing what kind
of activity I would see.
Part of being in a team is
everybody needs to be doing
as much as they
can in every direction
that they feel like they can.
Now, I'm just gonna wait
and see what comes in.
-Oh, there he is.
-I see him.
Joe's on his way back.
What's happening, buddy?
It's, uh, just a water
hole up the way, but...
a pod of three hippos in
there bobbing up and down
the whole time.
Guineafowl came.
Just missed by a little bit.
Yeah.
Nothing else.
Sorry, no action or
luck or sign, buddy.
I can see the
disappointment in ya.
It'll change.
Took me eight days to
make something happen.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
It'd be really nice to
be the food provider
for the group.
Just have to keep pushing
and wait for my chance
to get one shot.
That's all I want.
Kinda feel like she's
going to get sunburned.
It's not smart
working in that heat.
Oh she's good to go?
Give it a go.
Damn.
Is she just sinking 'em?
Is she giving them
a proper burial?
Think you have to be
already drawn and waiting.
You know, you can't see
the fish and then draw.
You gotta be drawn and waiting.
After staying there for
a few minutes, I realized
that there were telltale
signs of fish moving
beneath the water.
There were different
kind of bubbles
when the fish
would move through.
One.
Come on, come on, come on.
There's no chance.
Crazier things have happened.
I Watch Teal take
a few shots now.
I know she's a good shot,
but difficult to see them
in the water.
OK. I see 'em, I
see 'em, I see 'em.
Oh, Teal, here she goes.
Woo!
-2 Just one look at the last one?
-Yeah.
There's a window
here, I'm just gonna
look through the window.
Oh, I do not like this one.
Somebody was doing
some religious type stuff
in this room.
Kinda nice, but kinda
creepy all at the same time.
Look at the candles.
It's not like they're
gonna be missing it.
OK.
In this apocalyptic scene
that we're walking through,
there's just some
bad juju going on.
Thank you, Lord.
It gave me the creeps.
2 OK.
I see 'em, I see 'em,
I see 'em, I see 'em.
Oh, Teal, here she goes.
Woo! That's what
I'm talking about.
-Yeah!
-Yeah, Teal!
Woo!
It was truly a complete
shot in the dark
because I was
aiming into black mud,
but ran my hand down
the shaft of the arrow
and found that I had nailed
that catfish almost dead center.
-Yeah!
-Woo!
What a boss!
She proved me wrong.
I love that.
That's awesome.
You are an absolute superstar.
-Oh!
-Oy!
-Ooh, pull it out of the water!
Run!
I'm really proud of Teal,
you know, hats off to her.
There haven't been many
females on "Naked and Afraid"
that have killed with
a bow and arrow.
Good job, girlfriend.
-Way to go, Teal!
-Yeah, Teal!
Well done.
Oh, getting hard
walking through this.
Yeah. Oh, there's some
sharp stuff in here, man.
Wow.
Yep.
Tell you what, man,
I'm seeing a lot of reeds
-in the... creek bed now.
-Yeah.
It's like maybe we're
getting closer to water.
Yeah.
What the!
Oh, hey!
People keep showing
up at our doorstep.
What's going on?
Hey!
Yeah!
-Pleased to meet you, I'm Joe.
-Stee.
Really Wes!
Out of my peripherals, I
see, it's Wes coming up
over the hill.
Beautiful sight to see.
We expanded the shelter out
this morning to accommodate
just the six of us, so
the six of us would fit.
Now we're eight, so
it's almost like we're
back to square one.
-Nice meeting you.
-Hey, buddy.
I'm Waz. Nice to meet you, bud!
Wes.
What's up, Steve?
How you doing, bud?
-So good to see you.
-Nice to see you too.
I'm so proud of you.
I see big, old Waz.
I see Steven. It's
a super moment.
-Good to see those boys.
-Come on.
Why wait? Give
you a little shade.
Do you want a
hand with anything?
-Can we carry anything?
-Yeah, I'll take a hand
with anything you
feel like picking up.
100%.
-No crocs.
-We've been competing
with a crocodile all the time.
-Not much swimming for us.
-Going in, find a spot.
That's why the
boma's now a thing,
'cause there was
too much in there.
It's a bit surreal,
to be honest.
I never thought
in a million years
that I'll be sleeping in a
cage in the middle of Africa.
We wanna make sure
you have the space
-you want, Stee, so...
-Yeah.
It's awesome that
this many people
have survived such
a harsh environment,
but we have a lot
of people here now.
That's eight mouths to feed,
that's eight hungry stomachs,
-and a week left.
-Everyone is
as comfortable as
they can possibly be.
-Those are the rules.
Where's that damn fish?
Probably done.
All right. Right over there.
Yeah, I'll catch up.
Oh my God.
I really thought that
we were the final six,
and now we have
a group of eight.
And eight mouths
to feed is a lot.
And the fish I caught is just
not enough food for all of us.
Did everybody get a piece? OK.
That sample is good,
I'll take a full serving.
We still have a week
left and bigger teams
mean bigger challenges.
And we know we have
the biggest challenge
yet to go with this escape.
It's been tough out here.
Somebody who's
been here three times.
This is tough. This
Hell on Earth in Africa.
Any number of
things could go wrong.
It's hard to have eight people
and have all eight of 'em
on the same page.
This is one of the most
brutal environments
I've ever been in.
This is savage.
Everyone's pushed
to their limits,
and we still have
a long way to go.
There's no one
coming to save us.
We're on our own.
We need to get
out of this place.
Hopefully, there is a way
to escape this hellish prison.